Guide to the Ken Kennedy academic records, 1967-2007 MS 206
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series I: Centers, 1988-2007 (Boxes 1-16)
  - Subseries A: Center for Research on Parallel Computation (CRPC), 1988-1999
    - STC Plan. 1989-90. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - STC Plan: Center for Research on parallel Processing Plan. 1990. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - STC General File (Center File) (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - CRPC Research Plan. 1992. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Bibliography Notes. 1996. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Bibliography. 1996. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Latest draft - 1997 Bibliography (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Bibliography Notes (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Received 1997 Bibliography (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Requested - 1997 Bibliography (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence regarding 1997 bibliography (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - CRPC Annual Report - 1998. (1 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - CRPC Annual Report - 1998. (2 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - STC Directors Meeting. 1995. (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - EAC 1996 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Awards (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - NSF Recognition Award 1996 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - CRCC "Home Impact" Article (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Israel Galvan (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Wulf/Jennings (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Rotating EAC Letters 1995 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - EAC (new members) (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - EAC - Ex.tex (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - 28th Executive Committee meeting standards (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Plan 1989 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Proposal Guidelines (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Center Management - CRPC (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - EAC Rotation 1995 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Affiliated Site (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - CRPC Renewal Proposal. 1994. (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - CRPC Proposal (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Standards Document (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - CRPC 1996 Retreat (White Paper) (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - The Plan 1993 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - NAPA (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - NAPA/ABT (NSF) (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Abt for Dean (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - ABT/NAPA (NSF) 1995 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - "An Assesment of the National Science Foundation's Science and Technology Centers Program." 1996. (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Abc Assocates Inc. "An Evaluation of the NSF Science and Technology Centers (STC) Program." Volume I. June 1996. (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Abc Assocates Inc. "An Evaluation of the NSF Science and Technology Centers (STC) Program." Volume II. June 1996. (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Abc Assocates Inc. "An Evaluation of the NSF Science and Technology Centers (STC) Program." Volume III. June 1996. (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Abc Assocates Inc. "An Evaluation of the NSF Science and Technology Centers (STC) Program." Volume IV. June 1996. (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - CRPC Renewal Site Visit Handout. 1994 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - CRPC Renewal Proposal. 1991. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - CRPC Renewal Proposal. 1994. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - CRPC Annual Report. 1992. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - CRPC Annual Report. 1993. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Bibliographies (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - NAPA (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - NAPA Site Visit (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - NSF Site Visit Proposal Reviews (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Books (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - 1994 Site Visit Reviews (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - CRPC Packet Information (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - CRPC Site Visit. August 1996. (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Who Does What (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Research Categories (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - What It Is! (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - EAC Report - Wallach. Original, 1997. (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Annual Report (NSF and CRPC) (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - CRPC General (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - CRPC On-Line Tech Report. September 2005. (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Mary Wheeler (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Vicky (CS) Dean (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - El Messidi, Kathy (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Bob Lucas Site Visit. 9 March 1995. (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Almes' Visit. 24 March 1997. (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Visitors (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Piyush (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - SAIC Visitors. 17 February 1993. (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Danny Powell (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - 1997 CRPC Annual Report (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - CRPC NSF Proposal. 1997. (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - ASCI (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Director's Issues (Konisky's Mtg). 28 April 1999. (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - HPF User Group Meeting and Surveys. 1998. (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Books/ CRPC Ultra etc. (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - ASCI/DOE (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Rice Contribution to UH Proposal to ASCI for a Fluidization Institute (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - ASCI ASAP Level 2 - Strategic Investigations (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Compilers, Tools, and Runtime Technology for Terascale Systems. DOE/ASCI. 1998-2001. (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Request for Proposal ASAP-02 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Ken's Proposal Files (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Compaq External Technology Program. 1998. (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - House Conference Committee (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Department of Defense Questionnaire (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - ARPA - Vita(s) (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - CISE (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - CSTO Joint PI Meeting. 1995. (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Department of Defense Modernization Program (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - US Army Engineer Waterways Experiment Station (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Convex Debug Spec (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Convex (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Convex C2 Performance (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Convex - Parsec Technical (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Convex/Hysinger (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Convex Contract 1991 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Convex Agreement (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Convex Press Proposal (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Convex News Releases (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Convex Turbulance Machine (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Convex/STC Luncheon and Presentation (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - National Center for Supercomputing Applications (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Convex Sorensen (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - ARPA Support Letters (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Convex Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - The Computational Node for the Direct Solution of Turbulance 1990 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - CRPC 1999 Annual Report (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Compaq Visit Houston, TX, 19 June 1998 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Compaq (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Compaq Meeting, 1998-99 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Future Directors for the NSF Supercomputer Centers Program Report (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - 24 STC Annual Reports (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - HPCC Research Agenda (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Amsterdam (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - ICPP Transparencies, August 1993 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - CMU Talk (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - HPFF II Intro (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - DARPA PI Meeting - HPF (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Fortran D Slides (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Fortran System Site Visit, September 1993 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - CRPC Annual Meeting Slides. 27 January 1993 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Annual Meeting Slides. 27 January 1993. (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - CRPC Slides (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - GPCP Lecture (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Center Education Overview NSF Site Visit. September 1993. (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Fortran Overview. January 1993. (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - EAC Talk (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Center Overview Annual Meeting. January 1993 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - CRPC Annual Meeting Slides. 15-16 November 1990 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Center Overview (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Center Overview Interim NSF Site Visit. September 1993 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - General Center Slides from Harris (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Genome Site Visit (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Planning Meeting (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - AHPCRC Research Overview (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Model-based Compilation... (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Annotated Standards (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Center Overview. 1994 CRPC Renewal. (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Management. 1994 CRPC Renewal. (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Overview S and C Site Visit (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - DARPA Machine Ind. (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Unused Slides - Renewal Site Visit (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Fortran Overview - Renewal Site Visit (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Overview IBM Site Visit. 25 October 1991. (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Oberlech HPCC (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Mini-symposium Lecture (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Fortran Parallel Programming Project Site Visit. February 1991. (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Geophysical Computation Research Review (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - STC Site Visit. 15 February 1990 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - CISE II Site Review (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - CRPC Annual Meeting Research Review (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Minorities and Women 1994 Renewal (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - CRPC Overview Slides (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - NASA Visit 1995 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - DELTA (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Ken's Visit (CEWES) Dr. Radha (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Fox - Education (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Information Technologies (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - New Technology Integration Services from InfoMall (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - InfoMall Proposal (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - NSF Metacenter Report. February 1992. (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - NSF Interprocedural Proposal 1986 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Meta Center Proposal (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Rapid Prototyping of Synthetic Environments Proposal. 1998. (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - E-mail from Claudio Rebbi regarding "Lattice QCD." 6 May 1999 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - National Research Council (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Programming Environment and Training Activities Subcontract for Army Research Lab Major Shared Resource Center (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - NASA Visit. 22 August 1995 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Teleconference call. March 1994. (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - NASA/Rice Meeting. 20 June 1995 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Susan Gerhardt's Visit. 11 November 1992 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Bob Lucas (ARPA 3/9/95) (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - Richard's Workshop 8/95 Ken's Slides (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - NASA Visit. 22 August 1995 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - Rats Workshop Slides. 7/1996 (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - Prospects of Architecture - Independent Parallel Programming (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - Affiliates Meeting. April 1994 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - SIAM Tutorial. 22 February 1995 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - Annual Meeting Slides. 27 January 1993 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - CRPC Education Plan (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - DARPA Joint Meeting. September 1992 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - ICASE (talk) 26-30 July 1993 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Center Overview. 13 July 1995 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - ARPA-PI meeting. 19-20 January 1995 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - DARPA 16 March 1993 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - HPFF 29-30 January 1995 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Slides for SIAM HPF Talk (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - NHSE (Dongarra) February 1995 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Overview of Projects 1994 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - NSF Grand Challenge. 23-24 December 1992 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - NCSA 18-22 October 1993 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Education Slides, 1 Feb. 1993 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Scalable High Performance Computing Conference (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Debugging and the teraflop computer (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Why Interprocedural Analysis? (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - CRPC Presentations (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - NSE (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - NSE Board (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - NHSE Presentation (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - National High Performance Distributed Computing Consortium (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - National Computational Science Alliance Proposal (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - MADIC (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - National Software Exchange (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - CRPC/Kennedy PBM. 3 December 1995 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Fortran Tools Newsletter Series (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Scalable I/O Slide (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - CAPS (next meeting) (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - General - CAPS (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - CAPS/ CRPC Project (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - CAPS Advisory Committee (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - CRPC NSF Renewal. 1994 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - CRPC NSF Renewal. 1996 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Job Descriptions (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Retooling MRA Drafts (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - NCSC MRA Workshop (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - NOW (Jane Stutsman Meeting) 9 June 1995 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - CRPC Affiliates (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Education Programs (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - PACI/NCSA Proposal (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - CRPC Book (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Revised CRPC Book Chapters (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - CRPC/ARSP (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Open MP and HPF (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Compiler Infrastructure Slides (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - CRPC Interim Site Visit. 8-10 September 1993 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Subcontract under U.S. Department of the Interior (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - "Scientific Portals" Presentation (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Compilation Slides (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Compiler Technology Slides (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - CRPC Slides (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Virtual Grid Application Development Software (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Active Reliable Multicast on Application-Aware Grids (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - LACSI (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - NSF Planning from Congress - Gramm letter (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - CRPC Investigators. 18 January 1995 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Math Proposal (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Paper (bios) (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - CRPC - Bios - Various (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Congressional Letters - Budget Cut (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Assessment of NSF's Science and Technology Centers Program (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Sub Award Kit (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Congressional Business Office (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - CRPC Awards and Honors (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Notes from MRA Workshop. March 1995 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - CBO Report on HPCC (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Scalable I/O (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - National Institute of Standards (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Mailing List (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - HPF Meeting January 1996 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Education Meeting with Nora Sabelli (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - State of Texas Contract 1059 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Texas Brochures (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - CITI (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - CRPC Pamphlet (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - High Performance Computing (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - ARPA (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - CRPC Book: Status of Responses from Authors. 1 March 1999 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Department of Defense High Performance Computing Modernization Program (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Department of Defense Major Shared Resource Center (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Ken Kennedy Curriculum Vitae (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - CRPC Book Review Meeting Washington D.C. June 1999 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - CRPC 1995 Annual Report (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Reviews of Third Year Renewal Proposal. 20 August 1991 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Plans for Review of Sixth Year Renewal Proposal. 10 March 1994 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - ASCI Program Plan Draft (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - NCSA FY94 Program Plan Appendices. October 1993 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - CEWES MSRC PET Annual Report: Year 2. April 1997-March 1998 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - NSF's Science and Technology Centers Brochure (3) (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - "The Spend a Summer with a Scientist Program: An evaluation of program outcomes and the essential elements for success", July 1998 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - "NSF's Science and Technology Centers: Building an Interdisciplinary Research Paradigm", July 1995 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Human Genome Program by C.T. Caskey (Grant application), 1990 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Army High Performance Computing Research Center Site Visit Handbook, June 1989 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - CRPC Annual Report, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - CRPC Site Visit Handbook, July 1988 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - CRPC NSF Renewal Site Visit, September 1991 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - CRPC Annual Report, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - CRPC First Annual Research Symposium, August 1990 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - CRPC Plan, February 1990 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - CRPC Renewal Proposal., 1 July 1991 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - CRPC NSF Site Visit, February 1991 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - CRPC Annual Meeting, 15-16 May 1996 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - CRPC Renewal Site Visit, August 31-September 2, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - CRPC External Relations: Revised Two-year Plan and Budget, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Rice University and California Institute of Technology Proposal to the NSF, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Rice University et al. Proposal to Headquarters, ISA/LABCOM, Part III (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Rice University et al. Proposal to Headquarters, ISA/LABCOM, Part IV (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Rice University et al. Best and Final Offer to SA/LABCOM, Part IV (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Subseries B: HiPerSoft, 1998-2007
    - NCSA Teleconference. 3 August 2001 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - CCS DRC Review Report. 31 May 2002 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - caBIG Project. October 2003 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - RFA CA04-013 Integrative Cancer Biology Programs (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - LANL DRC (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Los Alamos CCS DRC Members and Resumes 2002 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Los Alamos National Laboratory (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - LANL DRC/PRC Meeting. Los Alamos, NM. 10 February 2004 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Los Alamos National Laboratory Overview. 2 May 2006 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Santa Fe Information Technology Laboratory - Planning Overview (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - LANL CCS DRC Read ahead Materials for February 10 Meeting. 2004 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Los Alamos Assessment Request. 12 December 2002 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - BioGrid Meeting. 19 February 2003 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - SFITL - Rice Commitment Letter (Dr. Gillis) 2002 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Messana, Nic. 2002 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Messana, Nic Reading File - Correspondence. 2002 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - LACSI Center of Excellence Call. 22 January 2004 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - LANL Prospectus for a Consortium for University Lab Partnering. 2003 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - SFITL/Senate Energy and Natural Resources Committee. 2004 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - New SFITL Bill and Joel press Release (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - SFITL Status and Plans Teleconference with J.R. Kirkland. 11 June 2004 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - LARP Institutes (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - ITL, LACSI, Q Teleconference. 27 September 2001 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Call from Jack Dongarra re: LANL. 2 October 2001 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - LANL/NM Congressional Staff re: ITL Meeting. 1 June 2001 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Meeting with Provost re: LANL/ITL. 13 May 2002 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - SFITL Briefing (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - SFITL Materials (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - SFITL - Proposal. 18 April 2002 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Meeting with Dr. Levy re: SFITL and Budget. 22 August 2002 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Meeting with Clay Sell of Senator Domenici's office. 15 July 2002 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Mathworks NDA. March 2005 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - VGrADS Site Visit Rice University. 28-29 April 2005 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - ORNL Incite User Agreement. March 2007 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - NCMI Advisory Committee Meeting at Baylor. 30 October 2004 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - NCMI Advisory Committee Meeting. 12 November 2005 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Rice/BCM/MDA - IBM Workshop. 6 October 2004 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Qasem, Apan. Post-Doc Position 2007 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Intel - CDA and License Agreement needed for ALF and DACS (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - National Instruments funding extension, 2007-2008 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Award Expiration Notices (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - HiPCAT Face-to-Face Meeting. 27 May 2005. (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - HiPCAT Meeting at U of H. 28 May 2004 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Press Release November 2002 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Compaq Labs (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Compaq Framework (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Compaq/Gillis/Gorry (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Compaq-Rice Research Support ($200k) 2002 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - HP Budget Meeting. 10 January 2003 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - HP Reception at Jones School. 9 August 2002 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Meeting with Peter Blackmore (HP/Compaq). 23 August 2002 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Meeting with Rob Schreiber (HP). 9 October 2003 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - HTC Luncheon with Carly Fiorina. 25 September 2003 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - HP Event at Rice. 23-24 April 2003 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - HP Godiva Project Contract DARPA BAA. October 2003 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Winston Prather's Visit to Rice University. 9 December 2003 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - HP Meeting Februray 2005 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Meeting to discuss UK-Texas Initiative. 16 May 2003 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Networked Science in Biology and Medicine (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Phone call with Richard Gibbs re: NCBC Second Round. 7 July 2004 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Meeting with Dr. Smith re: NCBC. 28 May 2004 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - NCBC (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Rice/TMC and State Life Sciences Teleconference. 1 November 2004 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Baylor Human Genome Center Meeting to discuss Proposed Collaboration. 2004 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - NCI Advanced Biomedical/Computing Center meeting. 29 August 2003 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Ken Calls George Weinstock at BCM. 30 July 2004 (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Meeting with Wah Chiu re: proposal. 12 January 2004 (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Meeting with Don Berry re: RFA NCI. 9 January 2004 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - BioGrid (Rice/Baylor/UH) 2004 (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - BioGrid Meeting, 19 Feb. 2003 (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - Meeting with Dr. Guerrero (MDACC) re: BioGrid/RTC Collaboration. 2004 (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - Schlumberger Meeting. 27 November 2006 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - "Scheduling Constrained Dynamic Applications on Clusters" (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - NIH BISTI Teleconference. 9 September 2003 (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - NIH RFA-RR-04-001. 2003 (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - Gigascale Design and Test focus Center (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - CGrADS - STC Site Visit Letter to Rita Colwell. March 2002 (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - CGrADS - STC - Site Visit Report. 26 October 2001 (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - Response to Reviews (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - GrADS - STC Proposal Reviews and Panel Summaries. 26 June 2001 (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - CGrADS - STC Proposal. 2 April 2001 (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - CGrADS - Panel Recommendation Site Visit (Box 10, Folder 82)
    - CGrADS (STC) Letters of Support (Box 10, Folder 83)
    - Year 1 Budget Reduction (Box 10, Folder 84)
    - CGrADS Site Visit Report. 26 October 2001 (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - CGrADS Response to Site Visit Report. 7 November 2001 (Box 10, Folder 86)
    - ET - Parallel Computing and AT - Biology Meeting. 10-11 December 1998 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - CGrADS Site Visit Demographic Info (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Center for Grid Application Software Research (CGrADS) NSF Site Visit. 25 Oct 2001 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - GrADS NSF Proposal. 12 January 1999 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - GrADS (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - CGrADS Pre-proposal Distribution Copy. 12 February 1998 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - CGrADS Pre-proposal Confidential Copy. 1998 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - CGrADS Master. 1998 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - GrADS Workshop in San Diego, CA. 7-8 February 2000 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - CGrADS Site Visit Planning Meetings (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - CGrADS Site Visit Planning Meetings (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - CGrADS (STC) Site Visit Agenda and Confirmations (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - GrADS Paper - printed on 30 August 2001 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - CGrADS: Annotated Draft Site Visit Agenda (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - CGrADS: Draft Site Visit Agenda (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - CGrADS STC Site Visit. 25-26 October 2001. (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - CGrADS STC Site Visit. 25-26 October 2001. (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - CGrADS - Industry Support - Microsoft (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - CGrADS Proposal/IT Partnership meeting 2001 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Handouts meeting with Dr. Gillis and Dr. Levy. 10 October 2001 (Box 11, Folder 20)